<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ayda</title>
    <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ayda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aydanichols.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ayda 1993</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-29-ayda-1993/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-29-ayda-1993/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I miss her.</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-03-i-miss-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-03-i-miss-her/</guid>
      <description>By Sara Nichols
I miss her laugh that could be heard across the room.
Her smile that could brighten anyone&amp;rsquo;s day.
Her love for every single person in the world, no matter how rude they were.
Her patience for my two sisters and me.
Her despise for rodents.
Her funny storytelling skills.
Her yummy crepes she would make every morning.
Her goofy personality that could make anyone feel better.
Her huge disgust for milk even though I loved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Things I Chose to Forget</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-03-the-thing-i-chose-to-forget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-03-the-thing-i-chose-to-forget/</guid>
      <description>By Sara Nichols
My last memories of her are the ones in her hospital bed Barely alive but not quite dead The wires and machines were breathing for her Everything else was just a big blur She couldn’t even recognize me or who I was And the huge ball inside her lungs, was the whole entire cause
I wish I could remember the last words she spoke Or the happy things before every noise she made was a croak But all I remember is the gloomy, sad, and terrible stuff That i&amp;rsquo;m almost starting to forget who my mom really was But people have told me that those memories weren’t really my mom It was just the cancer taking over her lungs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Day</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-12-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-04-12-your-day/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Varsity Bowling</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-02-20-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-02-20-bowling/</guid>
      <description>Sara placed first on the varsity bowling league!!! 135!!! Wow!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seventeen</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-02-19-seventeen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2021-02-19-seventeen/</guid>
      <description>During the last few years of Ayda&amp;rsquo;s life, she enjoyed keeping her friends, family, and students updated through her blog, facebook, instagram, and twitter. When she took the time to write, it is important to reflect and find meaning in what she wanted to tell us. She had a deep desire to serve. She was battling something and knew others would face the same challenges and tragic circumstances. She wanted very much to share with cancer survivors how she found hope, peace, and understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2020-03-01-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2020-03-01-five/</guid>
      <description>This site is devoted to the beautiful life of Ayda Nichols. Certainly from my perspective, the most beautiful soul to ever grace this world.
Anyone who ever had the pleasure of knowing Ayda I know your life will never be the same without her. My heart has an intractable pain. The pain is so big because it hurts from a spouses perspective and I also hurt for my three daughters. My girls will live in a world without the affection, tenderness, compassion, love, and wisdom of their mother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayda&#39;s Last Prayer</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2019-09-15-lastprayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2019-09-15-lastprayer/</guid>
      <description>Ayda’s Prayer (from audio which she left for Scott, Myriam, Maria)
Dear Heavenly Father,
Thank you, Lord, for this day. Thank you that you have allowed me to live one more day with my family. I really have enjoyed it. I can distinguish their needs, their anxieties, their concerns, everything that they’re going through. Please protect them.
Please protect Maria. Help her grow through this situation. I know it’s very, very sad and their heart is broken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayda&#39;s Prayer</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2019-07-31-aydas-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2019-07-31-aydas-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Ayda’s prayer from her 42nd birthday celebration:
Please Lord, help us to always remember how good you are. Even in the middle of all the darkness and all the difficult times that I’ve had to endure, you’ve surrounded me with amazing people. It’s just a little drop to show how great you are and how much you love us. You don’t leave us alone. You’re always holding our hand, even in the most difficult times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Breathe, just breathe; Come and rest at my feet”</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-10-31-breathe-just-breathe-come-and-rest-at-my-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-10-31-breathe-just-breathe-come-and-rest-at-my-feet/</guid>
      <description>Today as I was listening Jonny Diaz ‘s song, Breathe, I remembered that there is a place where I can go to catch my breath when I am worried or sad, the precious hands of God. Sometimes, the weight of the world oppresses my faith and my hope but when I lay still and in silence His presence lifts me up again.God by His unmeasurable grace has blessed me with an unbelievable peace through this challenging period of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“We are afflicted in every way but not crushed”</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-08-07-we-are-afflicted-in-every-way-but-not-crushed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-08-07-we-are-afflicted-in-every-way-but-not-crushed/</guid>
      <description>Summer break is over, family is back in Colombia and kids are back in school. Trying to get back into our regular routine but we always struggle organizing our sleeping schedule after weeks of sleeping in. In particular, for me, these past few nights especially have been hard to get a good night sleep. My husband says that I am a bit restless the night before my chemo. Maybe it still gives me a little anxiety the day of my chemo every three weeks, but I am mostly truly thankful for each additional day that has been added to my life by the resources that God has provided for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>update 🌷</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-03-14-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-03-14-update/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, here with an update. The first thing I have to say is that I’m fine and I feel very calm. My situation, although in words sounds like a death sentence, it’s not yet. There is hope and treatments for me. At this time the lung cancer grew again, but it is not super advanced (contained to the left lung and cerebellum), so we still have medicine to fight it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For My Girls</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-02-14-for-my-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-02-14-for-my-girls/</guid>
      <description>Why do I have peace about my girls?
Because they are not victims, they are blessed and triumphant in God.
He loves them
Psalm 139: 1-18 is a personal, unique and individual message from God directed to each one of us. He wants to place in our hearts the absolute certainty of His love for us. Understanding the detail and love that was given by God when he formed us is stunning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life&#39;s Purpose</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-02-01-lifes-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-02-01-lifes-purpose/</guid>
      <description>My name Is Ayda, on August 2012 I was diagnosed with lung cancer. Cancer made me look at life like I never had before. I have three kids and thinking about leaving them while they were so young consumed my heart for nights. Meanwhile our family turned to ask for prayers everywhere. I would hear from members of different churches letting me know they were praying for me daily. I was filled with peace and strength in a way that I could not understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focus on Jesus</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-02-08-focus-on-jesus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-02-08-focus-on-jesus/</guid>
      <description>Speaking about death is difficult period. Speaking about death when you know it is coming is even harder. During my first years with cancer I was moved by faith and hope. Even though I was ill, I didn’t see the end for me. Now is much harder to walk by hope. My cancer has advanced so much and it makes me feel like I am running out of time. I believe in the love of Jesus and I know that He is the one carrying me through this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping my eyes in Jesus</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-01-16-keeping-my-eyes-in-jesus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-01-16-keeping-my-eyes-in-jesus/</guid>
      <description>It has been a while since I felt like writing. I have been fighting a combination of sadness and disbelief through the past year. In a way is hard to understand my feelings because there is so much in my life to be happy and thankful, it feels unreasonable to struggle to find hope and joy. However, is also understandable since I reached the level in my cancer where I will not be in remission again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Reflection</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-01-01-a-deep-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2018-01-01-a-deep-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Prologue
In recent years I have had multiple thoughts and words moving in my mind as I go through a variety of emotions that have come and gone during this process with cancer. Some days I have many concepts that I would like to write and hide to reveal in the future, other days I feel as if I have nothing to say. The idea of leaving has created in me the desire to reflect with words who I am, so a part of me can be recreate in my absence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayda&#39;s Eight Worry Stoppers</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2017-11-25-aydas-eight-worry-stoppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2017-11-25-aydas-eight-worry-stoppers/</guid>
      <description> Pray first Rest in the Lord and wait patiently on Him. Reject anxiety. Act on it. Deal with it don&amp;rsquo;t dwell on it. Compile a worry list, review it. Evaluate your worry categories. Are some obsessions? Focus on today. Ask others to pray for you. Let God be enough. Seek God first.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release and Surrender</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2017-05-13-release-and-surrender/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2017-05-13-release-and-surrender/</guid>
      <description>I believe there is a uniqueness in all of us imprinted from The Father, a spiritual DNA or digital print. The search for our purpose, our mission, our happiness, can be a life lasting mission. I also believe that my relationship with Jesus is unique and different from yours. It is like the one I have with each of my daughters. I couldn’t tell you that I love one more than the other but I know that my bond is special and unique with each one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Completely surrendered into the hands of God</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2017-01-15-completely-surrendered-into-the-hands-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2017-01-15-completely-surrendered-into-the-hands-of-god/</guid>
      <description>This has been a very crazy time. We have had up and downs but every day I have been filled by the peace of God. I have given Him my complete trust and hope. He knows my hearth and I know He is walking with me through whatever is coming now. Battling my toughest cancer but I have already passed most odds that I have had against me.
Now, one day at the time fighting hard and making the best of everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of remission</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2016-12-31-out-of-remission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2016-12-31-out-of-remission/</guid>
      <description>This past July, as I celebrated my third year cancer free, I felt more grateful and also more humble than the year before. I have been blessed with enough health to continue a regular life, I am blessed with a precious family and there will not ever enough words to explain, how much every additional day I have been giving, after the first diagnose, means to me.
For the past three years, my life was able to go back in track, some kind of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Anniversary Cancer Free</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2016-07-11-third-anniversary-cancer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 20:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2016-07-11-third-anniversary-cancer-free/</guid>
      <description>These days I am struggling to stay positive and grateful for everything that God has done for me. I have been feeling some pain in the lower- left side of my chest. This apparently is caused as a side effect of the loss of part of my lung, chemo and radiation. I have been needing more medicine and exams than I would like, so my frustrations have grown.
Today however while I was in church I realized that it is my third year anniversary of being cancer free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living by faith</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2016-05-12-living-by-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2016-05-12-living-by-faith/</guid>
      <description>Living by faith is definitely easier said than done. When I was 20 I thought that meant to trust that the right man would find me and I could have my own happily ever after.
Almost two decades later l find myself searching for strength in my faith to believe that even through the great challenges that our family has faced I am walking in the plan of God.
Ironically, my two most likely options are: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spreading hope / Extendiendo la esperanza</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2015-07-09-spreading-hope-extendiendo-la-esperanza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2015-07-09-spreading-hope-extendiendo-la-esperanza/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the opportunity to visit again my beautiful Colombia. This trip was extra special because I had the chance to reunite with many members of my family. Not only did we celebrated major events (marriage and graduation), but I could also see in the eyes of many that there was a cause for celebration because the miracle of my recovery after my metastasis.
Our family reunions keep improving time after time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over 600 days cancer free!!</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2015-03-18-over-600-days-cancer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2015-03-18-over-600-days-cancer-free/</guid>
      <description>It might not be obvious to people why cancer patients keep counting their healthy days, especially random numbers like 615. Well, for me it turns out to be a reminder of what I have overcome and a burst of encouragement.
Eight months have passed since I started my job as a teacher and even though most of the effects from cancer are gone I need to continue with my checkups regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live without fear</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-08-23-live-without-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-08-23-live-without-fear/</guid>
      <description>Recently an acquaintance from Colombia died from cancer. She was diagnosed after me but her illness took her live in about a year. She was a sweet and loving woman, mother and wife and a specialist that worked with kids at my daughter’s school. It was inevitable to think that not too long ago I thought I was going to go before her.
One of the hardest things of cancer for people is to deal with the thought of something so unpredictable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survivor</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-07-19-survivor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-07-19-survivor/</guid>
      <description>Last week I went with my oldest daughter to the movies and saw “The Fault in Our Stars”, what a great movie. Coincidentally the next day was my first year cancer free anniversary and I was happy to “revive” many feelings on that day after watching this movie. I felt so connected to both of the main characters and felt like each one represented a side of me through this “fight”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspective</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-07-10-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-07-10-perspective/</guid>
      <description>The year before my cancer was found for first time I was going through the worst time in life that I can remember. My husband had lost his job; we had lost our home and our family was struggling to adapt to a complete new environment… my faith was crumbling. I thought I had made the right choices and did not deserve everything that was happening to us. Hope was gone and bitterness had taken its place in my heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autobiography</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-04-25-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-04-25-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>This is a paper I did for Taylor University on April 2014.
The first twenty
I was born in a small city of Colombia called Bucaramanga, the thirty-first of July on nineteen seventy seven. My mom became a single mother before she fulfilled her college education but she was determine to finish it as soon as I was born and find success on her own. During my first decade we moved twice, one of those times to Germany for a scholarship that my mom won to work on her Master’s degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hang in there!</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-02-15-hang-in-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-02-15-hang-in-there/</guid>
      <description>Today when I was driving to my counseling appointment I was thinking that in a couple of weeks I have my scanning tests again. I felt overwhelmed when I evaluated the fact that I needed to do this kind of exams for about five years more at least twice a year. It is not that the test itself is painful or difficult but it is this giant reminder that I am always at risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven months cancer free! If life gives you a beating, surprise life with a great comeback.</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-01-28-seven-months-cancer-free-if-life-gives-you-a-beating-surprise-life-with-a-great-comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2014-01-28-seven-months-cancer-free-if-life-gives-you-a-beating-surprise-life-with-a-great-comeback/</guid>
      <description>Next month I will have for second time after my brain surgery a series of exams to determine if my body is still cancer free. It has been almost a year and a half since I confronted for first time the obvious possibility of dying from this illness, leaving my husband and children, going through risky medical procedures and the other fears that as humans we hope to never have to face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Card</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-12-20-christmas-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 20:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-12-20-christmas-card/</guid>
      <description>Season’s greetings friends and family,
The gang is finally back together after Maria came back from Colombia to spend some time with us and we couldn’t be happier. We had our traditional Christmas photo shoot to select one picture that will represent what is going on in our life so we hope you enjoy it.
This year started pretty difficult while I was going through a strong treatment of chemo and radiotherapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invitation friends and family</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-08-26-invitation-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 20:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-08-26-invitation-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I hope this message finds you well, healthy and happy. As I have spent the past year fighting cancer, especially last month, spending tons of time resting and praying I decided to create a project that kept my mind busy and my spirit growing. I started to capture my thoughts and experiences into written words to keep a journal of this journey. My belief is that everything in life happens to make you a better person and to grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 25th, wow! Where did my summer go?</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-08-25-august-25th-wow-where-did-my-summer-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-08-25-august-25th-wow-where-did-my-summer-go/</guid>
      <description>On June 25th we left Colombia planning to visit 4 states, many friends and family and tons of fun. Well, talk about unexpected change of plans! After 2 really fun weeks with our family in Indiana and a great celebration of life party I ended up back again in the hospital for a headache with a new tumor found. If possible, this was even more difficult that the first time, all the family was devastated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need hope!</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-04-10-we-need-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 19:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-04-10-we-need-hope/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon I mentioned to the nurse how excited I was about having only 2 more chemo therapies left and how I don&amp;rsquo;t think I could have done this any longer. She mentioned that a guy in the next cubicle had been going through chemotherapy for 3 years, that just broke my heart. It made me realize that cancer as a chronic illness does not only slowly hurts your body but can crash your spirit too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standing strong</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-03-22-standing-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 19:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2013-03-22-standing-strong/</guid>
      <description>Finally my last cycle!
One more month, four chemos and this will be over. It has been a few rough months. This is the hardest thing I have ever done but I am still in victory. This process has taken everything I am, physically, mentally and spiritually. I wondered every day how people do it, some of them for years fighting for their life until the end.
I am definitely not the same person that I was because you can&amp;rsquo;t go through this without becoming stronger, kinder and wiser about what life really is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triumph is for the brave.</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-29-triumph-is-for-the-brave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 19:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-29-triumph-is-for-the-brave/</guid>
      <description>When my daughters have faced difficulty I don&amp;rsquo;t remember ever choosing the most valuable lesson if it implies a minimum level of pain. My first reaction when they face a challenge is to protect them, change the course of danger as far as I can and hope that it will never come around again. It is a reflection of love, going through fire doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a valuable lesson when we have to face it but it is just because we forget that the most important part of trial is triumph and that no one can take that away from us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another memorable day, honoring two brave women that fought cancer for me!</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-21-another-memorable-day-honoring-two-brave-women-that-fought-cancer-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 19:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-21-another-memorable-day-honoring-two-brave-women-that-fought-cancer-for-me/</guid>
      <description>My Aunt Martha is a breast cancer survivor, she was diagnosed last year and after a strong treatment and surgery she has recovered. Seven years ago, my Aunt Nubia passed away after a breast cancer comeback. Both of my aunts were less than 40 years old when they were diagnosed. Two of my uncles also on my mother’s side have fought against cancer in the past ten years. Needless to say our family is very aware about the need to watch over our health to detect any issues on time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiest day in the past months, I came back home!</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-13-happiest-day-in-the-past-months-i-came-back-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 01:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-13-happiest-day-in-the-past-months-i-came-back-home/</guid>
      <description>The day I had to go to Bogota for my surgery was a very sad day. My kids usually are calm when I have to travel, which is not very often, but on this occasion we all were really troubled. Isa specially had already showed us how upset she was just the day I explained to them I had to leave for a few weeks so the doctor could take “the little ball out” (this was the way I explained about my tumor).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biopsy Results</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-10-biopsy-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-10-biopsy-results/</guid>
      <description>Dear family and friends,
Yesterday we met with the oncologist and biopsy results confirmed what other tests had suggested about the tumor being cancer. The good news is that the tumor was completely removed during the surgery. Now we are looking to a 4 -6 month period of chemotherapy to reduce the risk of any other problems caused by the tumor before the surgery.
My recovery has been nothing but incredible,God blessed me with a very talented surgeon, friends and family that have been spoiling me, and a healthy body that has responded positively to a lot of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job 5:9</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-07-job-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-07-job-59/</guid>
      <description>Job 5:9: He performs wonders that cannot be fathomed, miracles that cannot be counted. God is great! Surgery was a success,He gave a wonderful team of doctors wisdom and ability beyond what I was expecting. I didn&amp;rsquo;t need any days in ICU and this morning the doctor came and took my oxygen off and the tube that was attached to my lung, made me sit and said: You look great and should go home soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to say “Thank you Lord” even when you don’t get what you want</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-08-learning-to-say-thank-you-lord-even-when-you-dont-get-what-you-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-08-learning-to-say-thank-you-lord-even-when-you-dont-get-what-you-want/</guid>
      <description>Today I finally had to make a decision about my surgery. I have been dealing with the insurance company for almost 3 weeks and I did not receive an approval for the robotic assistance so I wrote them and chose the conventional surgery because I need to move on. This means I will be spending a few days in intensive care after the procedure. I am calm, happy and confident that God is in control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News that changes your life</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-09-news-that-changes-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-09-news-that-changes-your-life/</guid>
      <description>To My Dear Friends,
Some days can change the way you look at life, today was one of those days for me.
Scott and I sat in front of a doctor while he explained that I need a surgery to remove a tumor believed to be cancer from my left lung.
WOW, not even 3 weeks of intensive exams and suspicions had prepared us to terrifying thoughts that the C word brings to your head but as the fear tried to take control of my mind, the sweetest voice whispered to my heart the exceptional promise that was given to me 7 years ago “For I know the plans I have for you,” declares the LORD,“plans to prosper you and not to harm you, plans to give you hope and a future”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving a place we used to call home.</title>
      <link>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-06-leaving-a-place-we-used-to-call-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 01:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aydanichols.com/post/2012-10-06-leaving-a-place-we-used-to-call-home/</guid>
      <description>my husband and I thought that as a couple that trusted and loved God we were prepared to go through an uncertainty period in life. When the time came we did not think it was going to last long. We didn’t feel as if it was the worst situation people could face but as big or small our cross was, it was ours. The company where my husband had worked for many years got hit by recession and closed its doors, leaving many unemployed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
